{
    "subject": "resource/Margo_Humphrey",
    "predicate": "ontology/training",
    "object": "resource/Stanford_University",
    "human_readable": "Margo Humphrey received training at Stanford University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9840113520622253,
            "question": "Did Margo Humphrey attend Stanford University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.981172502040863,
            "question": "Is Stanford University a place where Margo Humphrey received education?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9681413769721985,
            "question": "How might Margo Humphrey's training at Stanford University have influenced her career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8942249417304993,
            "question": "Where did Margo Humphrey receive training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8830170631408691,
            "question": "Are there any notable alumni from Stanford University in a similar field to Margo Humphrey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.882153332233429,
            "question": "What kind of training did Margo Humphrey receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7949169278144836,
            "question": "What university is associated with Margo Humphrey's training?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6052281260490417,
            "question": "What are some potential career paths for someone trained at Stanford University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48126864433288574,
            "question": "Is there any information about Margo Humphrey's field of study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3938051760196686,
            "question": "What are some of the resources and opportunities available to students at Stanford University?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Margo Humphrey received training at Stanford University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8356_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there any information about Margo Humphrey's field of study?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8356_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential career paths for someone trained at Stanford University?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8356_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What university is associated with Margo Humphrey's training?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8356_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8356_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Margo Humphrey received training at Stanford University\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Margo Humphrey attended Stanford Graduate School in 1971 while attending the Whitney Museum of American Art Summer Program, and she graduated from Stanford in 1972 with Honors and a Masters of Fine Arts degree in Printmaking."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide multiple references that Margo Humphrey received training at Stanford University. For instance, one of the documents states, \"She graduated from Stanford in 1972 with Honors and a Masters of Fine Arts degree in Printmaking.\" Another document mentions her participation in postgraduate programs there: \"[Humphrey] also participated in a postgraduate program at the Whitney Museum of Art in New York while attending Stanford.\" Therefore, the information supports that Margo Humphrey received training at Stanford University."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}